[{"id": 1549, "question": "*200 dead as Brazilian plane crashes in Sao Paulo Up to 200 people were dead after a passenger plane with 176 people aboard slid off the runway on landing and hit a fuel storage tank at Sao Paulo's Congonhas airport on Tuesday. Brazilian airline TAM said that 170 passengers and 6 crew were aboard the Airbus A320 flying from Porto Alegre in southern Brazil to Sao Paulo when it lost control on landing and slid off the wet runway. Brazilian news agency Folha reported up to 200 people were dead, including some victims on the ground. * _ Two people were killed Saturday in two separate plane crashes in the United States, media reports said. In Dayton, Ohio, a plane crashed on a runway of the Dayton International Airport while performing during the Vectren Dayton Air Show. The pilot, Jim LeRoy, w...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT TRUE as for the Kenya plane crash?", "options": ["The plane crashed after the plane took off.", "The cause of the crash was under examination", "114 passengers on board were killed including an African", "The place where the plane crashed led to many more deaths"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 618, "question": "\"Mama, when I grow up, I'm going to be one of those!\" I said this after seeing the Capital Dancing Company perform when I was three. It was the first time that my dream took on a vivid form and acted as something important to start my training. As I grew older and was exposed to more, my interests in the world of dance certainly varied but that little girl's dream of someday becoming a dancer in the company never left me. In the summer of 2005 when I was 18, I received the phone call which made that dream a reality: I became a member of the company dating back to 1925. As I look back on that day now, it surely lacks any sense of reality. I believe I stayed in a state of pleasant disbelief until I was halfway through rehearsals on my first day. I never actually expect to get the job. After ...\n\nQ: How many years has the Capital Dancing Company existed when the author received the phone call from it?", "options": ["180", "1925", "2005", "80"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1319, "question": "Recently educators have been questioning \"prep school\" (=preparatory school) where barely literate high school athletes get their transcripts by taking courses occasionally and sometimes by taking no courses at all. The athletes then go on to famous sports universities, where they exhaust their playing years before landing back on the streets without job opportunity or college degrees. The prep school scheme was meant to avoid academic qualification rules for college athletes made years ago by the National Collegiate Athletic Association. The N.C.A.A., which was slow to recognize the seriousness of the problem, has finally adopted policies to root it out. But those policies will not do the job unless everyone is involved, including prep schools and college athletics departments that still ...\n\nQ: We can conclude from the passage that the problems of prep school scheme might result from  _  .", "options": ["young people in poor neighborhoods who tend to ignore their studies", "many prep schools that carry out poor academic programs for high school athletes", "many college athletics departments that still recruit academically unqualified students", "school athletes, poor management of prep schools and irresponsibility of related college departments"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 661, "question": "The butterfly Ecological Park, which opened early this May, is located in Dabao Village in Longfeng Township of Pengzhou City, some 65 kilometers to the north of Chengdu downtown. The park, covering an area of 67 hectares, is more famous for a variety of butterflies living in _ surroundings and houses a collection of some 30,000 butterfly species. An ideal site for parents and kids alike to enjoy the sight of \"the flying flowers\" and the ecological area. A great variety of butterflies live in China, and Sichan and Yunnan are rich in butterfly resources. At present, 702 species have been discovered in Sichuan, where the number of butterfly species equals to the total of Europe. In the Longmen Mountain of Pengzhou City alone, there are more than 500 species. The butterfly Ecological Park, a ...\n\nQ: Why is The butterfly Ecological Park situated at the foot of the Longmen Mountain?", "options": ["Because the park has educational and cultural programs.", "Because the park has prepared many spring and summer activities.", "Because visitors can have a close look at butterflies in the park.", "Because butterflies of various species can live there naturally."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3161, "question": "One night recently , I was driving down a two-lane highway at about 60 miles an hour . A car approached from the opposite direction at about the same speed . As we passed each other , I caught the other driver's eye for only a second . I wondered whether he might be thinking , as I was , how dependent we were on each other at that moment . I was relying on him not to fall asleep , not to be put off by a phone conversation, not to cross over into my lane and bring my life to a sudden end . Though we had never spoken a word to each other , he relied on me in just the same way . Multiplied a million times over, I believe that is the way the world works . At some level , we all depend upon one another . Sometimes that dependence requires us simply not to do something like crossing over the dou...\n\nQ: The author considers  _  very important .", "options": ["driving alone on a dark road", "independence of people", "cooperation to identify SARS virus", "shared trust and cooperation"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 105, "question": "The United States is full of cars. There are still many families without cars, but some families have two or more. However, cars are used for more than pleasure. They are a necessary part of life. Cars are used for business. They are driven to offices and factories by workers who have no other way to get to their jobs. When salesmen are sent to different parts of the city, they have to drive in order to carry their products. Farmers have to drive into the city in order to get supplies. Sometimes small children must be driven to school. In some cities school buses are used only when children live more than a mile away from the school. When the children are too young to walk too far, their mothers take turns driving them to school. One mother drives on Mondays taking her own children and the...\n\nQ: The traffic in and around cities is a great problem because  _  .", "options": ["too many cars are being driven", "there are too many car pools", "people put fewer cars on the roads", "there is less gas"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 40, "question": "The first time Luca heard the Island of Inventions, he was very young, but the wonders he heard about sounded so unbelievable to him that they were forever kept in his memory. Since then, he never stopped searching clues which might lead him to that place of wonder. He read widely to collect information. Taking a little from here and there, he got quite a clear idea of what the Island was really like. It was a secret place, where all the great men learn and invent together. To be able to join that select club, you had to have created great inventions. Only then could you receive the invitation. To get a chance, Luca spend the years studying and inventing. Every new idea he got, he made it into an invention, and if there were anything he didn't understand, he would seek help. Soon he met ot...\n\nQ: Luca and other brilliant inventors around him shared a dream of   _  .", "options": ["being great inventors of worldwide fame", "being accepted as members of the Island of Inventions", "being inventors envied by members of the Island of Inventions", "being remembered for the contribution to scientific development"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1543, "question": "Ban Fur? Then Why Not Leather? Much to the displeasure of some local businesses, the City Council in West Hollywood, California, voted without opposition last week to ban the sale of fur products. Should laws be involved in this issue? Is it unfair to ban sales of fur, but not sales of leather and hides ? Animals Do Not Have Rights By Tibor R. Machan My view is that animals do not have basic rights. It is a matter of ethics and not of the laws of human societies. If animals had such rights as human beings do, they would have to be held responsible for killing fellow animals in the wild. That way of thinking about animals makes a category mistake. Using animals, including their fur or organs, to improve people's lives is acceptable. A Small Step Against Cruelty By Kate Carter Both fur and l...\n\nQ: What is Marc Bekoff's attitude towards sales of fur?", "options": ["Sympathetic.", "Careless.", "Tolerant.", "Opposed."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 682, "question": "For the first time in Hong Kong's history, an entertainer has been written into middle school textbooks. He is considered one of the best actors in Hong Kong. Yes, he is Chow Yun-fat. The example of his long hard struggle for success has been used in a chapter in a Hong Kong middle school textbook. Using his experience, students can learn to make the most of their time and to grab every opportunity to succeed. On hearing about this, Chow said happily, \"I really hope that my experiences can make young people understand that one should not be afraid of difficulties and setbacks , for they are the only way to success.\" Indeed, Chow has travelled a long and difficult path to reach his success. In 1955, he was born into a poor family in Hong Kong. When he was 17, he had to leave school. He work...\n\nQ: Chow felt   _   when he learned that he had been written into middle school textbooks.", "options": ["surprised", "shy", "sad", "happy"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1443, "question": "Onceupon a time there was a wise man that used to go to the sea to do his writing. Hehad a habit of walking on the beach before he began his work.One day he waswalking along the shore. As he looked down at the beach, he saw a human figuremoving like a dancer. He smiled to himself at the thought that someone woulddance on the beach. So he began to walk faster to catch up. As he got closer, hesaw that it was a young man and the young man wasn't dancing, but instead he wasreaching down to the shore, picking up something and throwing itinto the ocean. As he got closer, he called out, \"Good morning! What are youdoing?'' Theyoung man paused, looked up and replied, \"Throwingstarfishes in theocean.\" \"I guess I should have asked, why are you throwing starfishes in the ocean?\" \"The sun is up and the...\n\nQ: The writer told this story to show us   _  .", "options": ["how and where we can write a good article", "everyone can do something for the future", "wise men are sometimes stupid", "young men are in fact wiser than old people"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2885, "question": "Skateboarding has become one of several non-traditional activities that PE teachers around America are introducing to inspire kids to exercise regularly. Some PE classes feature in-line skating, yoga, and even rock climbing. Experts have called those types of activities \"the new PE\". Such activities are part of a larger effort to help kids develop lifelong fitness habits and to keep them from becoming overweight. Now, 9 million U.S. children and teens are overweight. Obesity can lead to health problems such as diabetes and heart disease later in life. \"Our children and youth are becoming unhealthy and obese,\" says Johnson. \"Skateboarding is a great activity that keeps kids doing physical movement and gives them new skills and interest.\" Some schools don't allow skateboarding because they s...\n\nQ: What life lesson do kids learn from skateboarding?", "options": ["To succeed in life you have to learn skateboarding.", "You will succeed in life if you don't give up.", "Only after failing 600 to 900 times can you succeed.", "There is no hard work after learning skateboarding well."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 67, "question": "New research at Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis shows that people who struggle with mood problems or addiction can safely quit smoking and that kicking the habit is associated with improved mental health. Cavazos-Rehg, an assistant professor of psychiatry, found that quitting or significantly cutting back on cigarette smoking was linked to improved mental health outcomes. Quitting altogether or reducing by half the number of cigarettes smoked daily was associated with lower risk for mood disorders like depression, as well as a lower likelihood of alcohol and drug problems. \"We don't know if their mental health improves first and then they are more motivated to quit smoking or if quitting smoking leads to an improvement in mental health,\" Cavazos-Rehg said. \"But either...\n\nQ: Which type of writing is the article likely to be?", "options": ["Science fiction", "A health report", "An education report", "A news report"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 913, "question": "HOGN KONG--Nine out of 10 Singapore citizens returned dropped wallets with money in them,but in Hone Kong only three out of l0 wallets were returned in an honesty test carried out in Asian cities by Readers Digest . Larger cities did worse while in general people in smaller places returned secretly planted wallets,results from the experiment showed. Readers Digest secretly scattered 140 wallets all over Asia,each with a name,address and phone number,family pictures,notes and money in it. The magazine workers then watched to see what happened.South Koreans in Seoul returned six out of the ten dropped wallets,while those in Inchon returned eight. 50 percent of Be dropped wallets were returned in Bombay,Bangkok,Taipei and Kajang in Malaysia,with most people saying they would not keep what was...\n\nQ: How many of the dropped wallets in Asian cities were returned?", "options": ["About 60.", "About 80.", "56.", "42."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2702, "question": "Hubert Joseph Schlafly was an electrical engineer who helped change the way actors, politicians and other people speak on television. In 1950, he and two other men developed the teleprompter. One co-worker, Fred Barton, was an actor. He had an idea for a tool that would help television actors read their lines without having to memorize them. The other co-worker was Irving Kahn. He worked as vice-president of radio and television at 20thCentury Fox. The first teleprompter involved a person who held a long piece of paper printed with big letters. As the actor read the lines, another person would move the paper ahead on the device . The teleprompter was first used on a television program called \"The First Hundred Years.\" Later versions used television screens to show the words that were to be...\n\nQ: When Hoover started to give his speech,   _  .", "options": ["he forgot to turn on the teleprompter", "he decided to stop using the teleprompter", "people didn't know he used a teleprompter", "people didn't think the teleprompter would work"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1993, "question": "On the morning of November 18, 1755, an earthquake shock Boston. John Winthrop, a professor at Harvard College, felt the quake and awoke. \"I rose\", Winthrop wrote, \"and lighted a candle, looked at my watch, and found it to be 15minutes after four.\" John Winthrop hurried downstairs to the grandfather clock. It had stopped three minutes before, at 4:12. Except for stopping the clock, the quake had only thrown a key from the mantel to the floor. The clock had stopped because Winthrop had put some long glass tubes he was using for an experiment into the case for safekeeping. The quake had knocked the tubes over and blocked the pendulum .Winthrop, therefore, had the key on the floor. The quake had thrown _ forward in the direction of the quake' s motion by a shock coming from the northwest, per...\n\nQ: Professor Winthrop ran downstairs because he wanted to know what had happened to  _  .", "options": ["the clock", "his grandfather", "the key", "the glass tubes"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 709, "question": "Children grow quickly, especially their feet, but many families cannot buy new shoes each time a child needs them. As a result, about 300 million children around the world go barefoot. Those children risk picking up diseases and parasites from the soil. An American man may have a solution for those barefoot kids -- a shoe that grows with the child. Kenton Lee is the creator of The Shoe That Grows. He explains how the shoe works and how it is able to last so long. \"It grows in three places: the front; it can also grow on the side with Velcro; and on the back with our buckle. It can last up to five years. The bottom is compressed rubber like tire rubber. The top is just high-quality leather.\" The shoe comes in two sizes: small that fits children aged 4 to 9 and large for children aged 9 to 1...\n\nQ: What does Para. 4 mainly talk about?", "options": ["How the shoes work.", "How Lee got his inspiration.", "How to make the new shoes.", "Where to order this kind of shoes."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2676, "question": "Science Fiction The science fiction type of entertainment is considered by most to be fathered by Jules Verne (A Journey to the Center of the Earth and Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea) and H. G. Wells (The Time Machine and The War of the Worlds). Sci-Fi, as it is commonly shortened, is a fictional story in which science and technology have a significant influence on the characters and plot. Many such works are guesswork about what the future holds and how scientific findings and technological advances will shape humankind. Writing in the late 1800s, Jules Verne was remarkably successful in his 10 guesses about future technologies of air conditioning, automobiles, the Internet, television, and underwater, air, and space travel. Unbelievably, of all places from which to choose, Jules V...\n\nQ: From the passage we can learn that   _  .", "options": ["Nineteen Eighty-Four adopted some popular terms", "H.G. Wells predicted the Internet in the late 1800s", "Cape Canaveral was mentioned in Jules Verne's fiction", "Star Trek movie series were based on space exploration"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1615, "question": "Dear residents of Molten, We can't keep silent in the current wild situation when prices for all existing products are skyrocketing unbelievably. The enormous figures on price tags for food products have caused a real panic. We've perfectly realized that, and that's why we have kept bread prices affordable for all this time. At the moment all our reserves are exhausted. Stocks of bread-baking ingredients such as flour, sugar, butter and the like are running out. To buy what we need at reasonable prices is virtually impossible today. However, we all need bread every day, which means we will be forced to buy everything we need at much higher prices. The cost of bread closely depends on ingredients. Another financial crisis has led to a 300-percent increase of prices for butter, vegetable oil...\n\nQ: In this open letter Figaro explains to the people of Molten that   _  .", "options": ["they can no longer supply bread", "the price of bread will be three times as high", "they need their help in holding down prices", "it will have to close down"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 175, "question": "A gentleman put an advertisement in a newspaper for a boy to work in his office. Out of the nearly fifty men who come to apply, the man selected one and dismissed the others. \"I should like to know,\" said a friend, \"the reason you preferred that boy, who brought not a single letter--not a recommendation ,\" \"You are wrong\" said the gentleman. He had a great man. He wiped his feet at the door and closed the door after him, indicating that he was careful. He gave his seat immediately to that old man, showing that he was kind and thoughtful. He took off his cap when he came in and answered my questions, showing that he was polite and gentlemanly. \" All the rest stepped over the book which I had purposely put on the floor.\" He picked it up and placed it on the table; and he waited quietly for h...\n\nQ: _   was the very person the gentleman preferred.", "options": ["He who has a great many letters", "He who had no letters", "He who wiped his feet before entering the room", "he who was careful, kind , polite and thoughtful"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 831, "question": "Among the many differences between Western and Chinese cultures, table manners are one of the most noticeable differences. Westerners often make mistakes at the table in China or in a Chinese home. In order not to have an embarrassing experience, here are some things to consider next time you are eating with some Chinese. Step1: Keep in mind that food is shared. It is one of the biggest differences between Chinese and Western eating habits. In China a few dishes are placed in the center of a table and shared by all. Also, you should offer thanks when a Chinese host takes food from one of the dishes on the table and places it on your plate. Refusing it would not be polite even if you are full. Step2: Respect the chopsticks. The chopsticks are the single most important tool at a Chinese tabl...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of writing the passage?", "options": ["To let the world get a full understanding of China.", "To introduce table manners among different cultures.", "To introduce Chinese table manners to Westerners.", "To introduce how Chinese table manners came into being."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2331, "question": "A weather system known as a polar vortex brought dangerously cold weather to large parts of the United States this week. A polar vortex is a cold, thick low pressure system. The air turns counter-clockwise when on the move. The polar vortex started up in Canada. After crossing the border, it moved deep into the southeastern United States. The polar vortex brought the coldest temperatures in more than 20 years to many areas. Alice Jenkins lives in Washington D.C. \"I have a coat on. I have three sweaters. I have two blouses. But I don't feel like I have anything on.\" Another woman, named Amanda, lives nearby in Maryland. \"It's D.C. It's not supposed to be this cold.\" The extreme weather started with a low-pressure system near the North Pole. The Arctic air was pushed as far south as Alabama ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements about the polar vortex is NOT true?", "options": ["It came from around the North Pole area.", "All the places it swept across became extremely cold.", "It caused Washington,", "It caused great losses in the U.S."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3396, "question": "Women love shoes! They will sometimes go to look for the perfect pair of shoes to wear only once with the perfect outfit or the fashion of the day. Once worn, these fashionable designer shoes may spend weeks, months, or years in the closet without being worn again until another special occasion comes up. With that said, are expensive designer shoes really worth their cost? Historically, shoes were invented to free feet from sharp rocks, hot sands, and blisters. Shoes were made to be simple and functional, with tough leather soles and straps. As society became more sophisticated , the role of shoes changed; shoes were made to add status to the wearer. Shoe designers began to work on the production of fashion shoes for the wealthy; shoes meant more for show than for practical use or simplici...\n\nQ: When shoes were first made, their main use was to   _  .", "options": ["increase the wearer's image", "protect the wearer from discomfort", "make the wearer more noticeable", "show the simplicity of life"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 660, "question": "The butterfly Ecological Park, which opened early this May, is located in Dabao Village in Longfeng Township of Pengzhou City, some 65 kilometers to the north of Chengdu downtown. The park, covering an area of 67 hectares, is more famous for a variety of butterflies living in _ surroundings and houses a collection of some 30,000 butterfly species. An ideal site for parents and kids alike to enjoy the sight of \"the flying flowers\" and the ecological area. A great variety of butterflies live in China, and Sichan and Yunnan are rich in butterfly resources. At present, 702 species have been discovered in Sichuan, where the number of butterfly species equals to the total of Europe. In the Longmen Mountain of Pengzhou City alone, there are more than 500 species. The butterfly Ecological Park, a ...\n\nQ: The author mentioned Europe in the essay to   _  ?", "options": ["stress that Sichuan has plenty of butterfly resources.", "state that a large number of butterflies live in Europe.", "tell readers that more than 500 species of butterflies live in Europe.", "emphasize that Europe is less famous than the Longmen Mountain."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2263, "question": "There is an English saying that goes, \"he who laughs last, laughs the hardest.\" High School Musical star and teen heartthrob Zac Efron is laughing a lot these days. As a young boy, Efron was picked on in school because he was always the smallest in his class and teased because he had a big space between his teeth. In the sixth grade, Efron's basketball team made it to the league championships. In double overtime , with three seconds left, he rebounded the ball and passed it to the wrong team! They scored and his team lost the game. But history, as they say, is a thing of the past. Now at 21, Efron is one of People magazine's 100 Most Beautiful People, graces the cover of Entertainment Weekly, Hollywood's most influential magazine, and is traveling the world promoting the third High School ...\n\nQ: What did Zac Efron do when he was laughed at?", "options": ["He couldn't accept the fact in the beginning, so he escaped.", "He was so angry that he shouted at the person who teased him.", "He cried and told the whole matter to his father to get comfort.", "He cheered himself up and used it as motivation to move on."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 36, "question": "A rare butterfly has been discovered in Britain for the first time in 60 years,having moved from Eastern Europe.The only previous record of a wild yellow-legged Tortoiseshell in Britain was in 1953,when it was seen just once in Sevenoaks,Kent.Several weeks ago,there were already four confirmed sightings,along the East coast in Norfolk,Suffolk and Kent,and six further reports of the butterfly in coastal areas. Conservationists are very excited about the sightings,which are rare in the butterfly world. The butterflies are thought to have flown on easterly winds across Europe in the last few weeks.The large and colourful insect mainly lives in Eastern Europe.In recent years,it has spread into Scandinavia and its number increases rapidly during warm weather.Also known as the Scarce Tortoiseshe...\n\nQ: These rare butterflies usually live in  _  .", "options": ["Eastern Europe", "Norfolk,Suffolk and Kent", "coastal areas", "Sevenoaks,Kent"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 562, "question": "The USA Well, imagine how my sister felt when she went off for the first time to New York for a business trip. After a few days she was still amazed at how friendly everyone was to her until she took a taxi back to her hotel one night. First she gave just the name of the hotel, but when asked she said the address too. Then she was asked how to get there, but of course she didn't know. Imagine how frightened she was when the driver started shouting at her for not knowing the way. The UK A friend was in London for a conference. He took a taxi and there were no problems: the driver knew the way and was very cheerful. The problem started when he realized he had stupidly left his laptop on the back seat! He called the company up and, in a panic, went straightaway to their Lost and Found office....\n\nQ: What do the three stories have in common?", "options": ["They are all about taking a taxi.", "They are all about business trips.", "They are all about great services.", "They are all about the author's family."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2151, "question": "With thousands of waterfalls across the world, it is difficult to choose the best but the following list contains some of the world's most amazing and beautiful ones! Iguazu Falls-The Iguazu Falls is located on the border of Brazil and Argentina and it is well-known for its scenic beauty. Though it is just about 89 meters high, it ranks as the fourth best waterfall in the world because of its beauty. The U-shaped cliff in the waterfall which is known as the Devil's throat is the most striking feature of the waterfall. Angel Falls-The Angel Falls, named after its discoverer James Crawford Angel, is the world's highest waterfalls, falling from a height of 979 meters. It is located in the Bolivar state in Venezuela. A unique feature of the falls is that most of the water falling down gets blo...\n\nQ: The similarity between the Tugela Falls and the Niagara Falls is that  _  .", "options": ["they both lie in South America", "their height is nearly the same", "they have the same source", "they both consist of several waterfalls"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 326, "question": "How will you celebrate New Year's Eve? By having a party with your classmates? Going to the karaoke for a singing competition? Many people around the world celebrate the day. Let's have a look at what people in other countries do. In the United States, thousands of people jam into Times Square in New York to welcome in the new year at midnight. The change from New Year's Eve and New Year's Day is very exciting. People count down the seconds to welcome the new day as the New Year ball slowly gets down and lights up the area. In Spain, when the clock strikes midnight, everyone eats 12 grapes. They eat one grape for each toll to bring good luck for the next 12 months of the new year. In Scotland, fireworks are set off in front of the Edinburgh Castle. Immediately after midnight, people sing A...\n\nQ: People in the US don't_when on the New Year's Eve.", "options": ["eat 12 grapes", "go to the Times Square", "count down the seconds", "get excited"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2809, "question": "A lot more people are about to get a chance to buy Google Glass. It's the Internet-connected eyewear that has become the hottest sale. Google will sell the \"Explorer\" version of Glass to any U.S. person who places an online order for the device beginning at 9am. PDT April 15. The product will cost $1,500. Google is saying how many sets of Glass will be available during the limited-time offer. This version of Glass, though, still isn't the perfect product that Google hopes to sell in stores later this year. For now, Google is still trying to recruit more people willing to serve as volunteers for its attempt to build a wearable device that features some of the same feature as a smart phone. \" Our Explorers are moms, bakers, surgeons, rockers, and each new Explorer has brought a new view that...\n\nQ: Google is still trying to recruit more volunteers to   _  .", "options": ["improve their products", "sell their products", "advertise their products", "wear their products"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2276, "question": "I have a painfully vivid memory of my first homecoming from college, in December 1983. After three whole months away, I was back home with my brand new opinions, attitudes and tastes. How could they watch such terrible television programs? I, the English Literature major with Shakespeare and Milton and James Joyce, could hardly bear to sleep under the roof of a house whose few bookshelves held thrillers and bound editions of the Reader's Digest. I'm sure my family was glad to see the back of me when, at the end of the holiday, I packed up my books and headed back up to university in the north of England. But the next year must have been even more painful to my parents: I didn't show up at all. Now, I don't think there's anything wrong with young people spending a little time away from thei...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the text?", "options": ["Pleasant memories about Christmas", "Horrible things happened in the past", "Interesting memories about Christmas", "Share with you some of my Ghosts of Christmas Past"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3268, "question": "If you are ever planning to buy a telescope and want to get yourself involved in astronomy it is always a good idea to know a bit of the sky.Get acquainted with a few constellations so that it will be easier for you to spot the constellations when you are using your telescope. It's a good idea to buy a few magazines on astronomy to help you to get familiar with the constellations in the sky and also read a few reviews on the different types of telescopes in the market.This will help you gather all the information that is out there regarding telescopes and what people have to say about them. It's advisable to go in for a pair of binoculars before you buy your first telescope so that you can get used to spotting constellations before your view of the sky is narrowed down.This will also help ...\n\nQ: What do we know about the refracting telescope?", "options": ["It looks very elegant.", "It refracts light by an eye piece.", "It has clear images without any lenses.", "It is not convenient to take along for its size."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3335, "question": "Japan Earthquake and Tsunami :How to Help For readers interested in contributing to help victims of the earthquake and tsunami that struck Japan and the Pacific region,here is a list of contact information and links for some agencies that plan to provide relief. THE JAPAN CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL EXCHANGE The Japan Center for International Exchange has set up the Japan NGO Earthquake Relief and Recovery Fund.Half of the money raised will go to support six Japanese NGOs currently at work in the disaster area and half will be retained to support the longer term recovery. AMERICAN RED CROSS Red Cross officials say donors can text REDCROSS to 90999 and a $10 donation will automatically be charged to donors' phone bill,or donations can be made directly on its Web site. B'NAI B'RITH INTERNATIONA...\n\nQ: Which group can provide food and shelter?", "options": ["THE SALVATION ARMY.", "GLOBALGIVING.ORG.", "B'NAI B'RITH INTERNATIONAL.", "AMERICAN RED CROSS."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1621, "question": "Your children's teacher will be providing extra time for test preparation. This school year's test will be held on January 8 and 9. The test preparation time is open to all students, and we strongly encourage your children to attend. This year we are changing the time for our test preparation: it will be on Thursday mornings from 8:10 to 8:50. This helps children who ride the bus and cannot stay for the after-school period. It also helps avoid conflicts with after-school activities. Danielle and Marina will be working with the recent new test takers 6 days on the following Thursdays: 15th, Nov; 29th, Nov; 6th, Dec; 13th, Dec.; 20th, Dec. and 3rd, Jan. Besides the test preparation lectures on these dates, teachers are already putting test preparation into their usual courses. We are finding...\n\nQ: Parents should   _   at home.", "options": ["prepare good meals for their children", "read more books with their children", "ask their children not to spend too much time on reading", "encourage their children to read more books fit for them"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 805, "question": "Studies show that you may be lied to every day anywhere from 10 to 200 times. We say, \"Nice song.\" \"Honey, you don't look fat in that, no.\" But another study showed that strangers lied three times within the first 10 minutes of meeting each other. We lie more to strangers than we lie to coworkers. Men lie eight times more about themselves than they do other people. Women lie more to protect other people. If you're married, you're going to lie to your wife/ husband in one out of every 10 communications. If you're unmarried, that number drops to three. But look, if at some point you got lied to, it's because you agreed to get lied to. Truth about lying: lying's a cooperative act. Not all lies are harmful. Sometimes we're willing to lie for the sake of social dignity , maybe to keep a private...\n\nQ: The examples of kids lying in the passage show   _  .", "options": ["lying is a sign of intelligent development", "lying is good for children's growing up", "at what age children begin to tell lies", "9-year-old children are masters of lying"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1928, "question": "Are you hard-working? Do you like to meet people? If your answer is \"Yes\", then we have a job for you as a waiter. Call AL Hotel at 556779! (2) SUMMER JOB Do you like to talk with people? Do you like to write stories? If you want to work for our magazine as a reporter, please call Karen at 558366. (3) HELP WANTED Do you like babies? Can you look after one baby for two days? If you are sure to take food care of it, call us at 766588. $80 or more. Today! Hurry! (4)CLEANER WANTED Can you make a large house clean and tidy? If you hope to get the job paid at $20 once, call us this evening 18:00-20:00. Tel:633800...\n\nQ: _  are needed in AL Hotel.", "options": ["Cleaners", "Baby-sitters", "Reporters", "Waiters"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3027, "question": "While elephants are respected by the people of Thailand, they are also used as beasts of burdens . Today, these majestic animals are extensively used to help carry wood for the logging industry. It is therefore nice to hear that on National Elephant Day the mighty mammals are treated like a king, and served with meals fit for a king. One of the biggest celebrations took place at the Pattaya Resort in Thailand's Chonburi Province. Fifty-two elephants, some wearing beautiful clothes, arrived bright and early for the big day. Each was first blessed with holy water by a professional elephant rider and then led to the grand feast, which served an unlimited supply of their favorite treats--bananas, dragon fruits , pineapples, assorted melons, apples and the list went on and on! The elephants ate...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the text?", "options": ["Elephants are protected very well in Thailand.", "Elephants also face the risk of being killed in Thailand.", "The number of elephants is increasing gradually in Thailand.", "Elephants could enjoy a grand feast every week in Thailand."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2594, "question": "Sometimes it is difficult to talk to taxi drivers. They must give all their attention to the road as they work out the shortest way to the place where you are going. However, passengers from Wangfujing were in surprise when they took a taxi. The driver just would not stop talking - in English. Organized by the Cultural and Education Section of the British Embassy, \"Dare to Speak\" examines if Chinese people will speak English in \"real-life\" situations. Matthew Knowles, an acting student from South Carolina at Beijing Film Academy, acted the part as the \"driver\". He collected six passengers on Saturday morning, most of whom were female white-collar workers. \"Of course they were surprised at first, wondering why I'm driving a taxi, and wondering whether this is a real taxi, but then most of t...\n\nQ: The purpose of the project \"Dear to Speak\" is to   _   .", "options": ["attract more foreigners to start business in China", "draw Chinese people's attention to IELT", "remind language learners of the goal of learning", "give more chances for English learners in China"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 110, "question": "Welcome to Coteborg University Coteborg University is one of Sweden's largest and most popular universities. We are very proud of this and believe that there are several reasons for our popularity. The principal reasons we believe to be the high quality of our education and research and the broad range of courses that we offer. In addition to this, Coteborg University provides an attractive and exceptionally high-standard study environment. Most parts of the university are situated in the city centre and this enriches city life as well as student life. Coteborg has a lot to offer its students: it has a rich and varied cultural life with many theatres, concerts and festivals. For those looking for outdoor life, forests and vast recreation areas are not far away from the city centre; the sea...\n\nQ: The main reasons for Coteborg University's popularity according to the passage is   _   .", "options": ["the high quality education and research and the wide range of courses", "the convenient traffic", "its excellent location and fast developing economical environment", "famous professors and friendly students"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1588, "question": "In 1969 I was a young girl working in Toronto. I was from a small town in Ontario and had just moved to the big city about three months earlier. It was one week before Christmas and I was going home on the last streetcar of the evening. I remember looking at my paycheque and asking myself how it was going to endure. At that time in my life I hardly had enough money to exist on. Bread for supper and oatmeal for breakfast was the only way I kept hunger at bay. I got off the streetcar and started walking up the street, when I suddenly noticed a man was running after me. I stopped, turned around, seeing that he was black. I _ , \"What do you want?\" The man answered in a soft voice, \"I am returning your wallet. You left it on the streetcar seat.\" Because of that man's thoughtfulness, I was allow...\n\nQ: Why was the black man running after the writer?", "options": ["To rob her.", "To scare her.", "To make friends with her.", "To return her wallet."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3496, "question": "Do you know how to play a game called \"Musical Chairs\"?It is easy to play and most people enjoy it. All you need are some chairs, some people and some way of making music. You may use a piano or any other musical instrument, if someone can play it. You may use a tape recorder. You can even use a radio. Put the chairs in a row. The chairs may be put in twos, back to back. A better way is to have the chairs in one row with each chair facing in the opposite direction to the chair next to it. The game is easy. When the music starts, the players walk round the chairs. Everyone goes in the same direction, of course, they should walk in time to the music. If the music is fast they should walk quickly. If the music is slow, they should walk slowly. The person playing music cannot see the people in...\n\nQ: When the music starts,the players must   _  .", "options": ["run about the room", "get down", "walk around the chairs", "sit on the chairs"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 993, "question": "In the United States, the legal age to drink alcohol is twenty-one --- one of the highest in the world. Americans debate whether _ should be lowered, or whether young drinkers would only drink more. In parts of Europe, the legal drinking age for beer, and sometimes hard liquor, is sixteen. Yet France may raise the age limit for beer and wine sales to eighteen, the same as for hard liquor there. Rules on alcohol differ from college to college in the United States. Many schools require all first-year students to take an alcohol prevention and education program, often given online. Some have a \"zero tolerance\" policy where alcohol is banned from all buildings. Parents are informed of violations and students may be suspended . At the University of Virginia in Charlottesville, permission is nee...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["Underage drinking is very popular in the US.", "Alcohol is forbidden in colleges and universities.", "Many students completed an alcohol education program in the US.", "It's hard for an international student to enter the US again if he breaks the rules."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1591, "question": "The college entrance exam is not only a big challenge for Chinese high school students, but also a very important exam in the lives of South Korean students. Although the long, cold winter has already started in South Korea, the annual national exams have made the atmosphere very heated. More than 675,000 South Korean high school graduates took the college entrance exam last Wednesday. They usually take exams in Korean, maths, sociology , history and foreign languages. Officially there is one college place for every 1.33 students. But because all the students want to go to the top universities in the country, the competition can reach one place for 10 students. The students want to attend these colleges for both their famous names and better job opportunities. Because students face fierce ...\n\nQ: We can infer that there are almost   _   college places for high school graduates.", "options": ["675, 000", "507, 520", "500, 000", "600, 000"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 762, "question": "We've all heard the phrase \"love is patient\", but one couple in prefix = st1 /Michigan, took this phrase to a whole new level. On Monday, February 13, Willard Mason sat down to talk about his relationship with the love he lost more than 60 years ago. Good fortune and fate recently helped the couple reunite. In 1941, Willard Mason and Llah Ost, both senior 2 students, became engaged to be married and began planning their lives together. But Willard moved away to work at Willow Run Bomber Plant, where he met and fell in love with a woman named Helvi. He broke off his long distance engagement to Llah and married Helvi in 1942. Llah later found love with someone else. Both had happy marriages and raised families. Then, in 2003, Helvi died. A year later, Willard found himself back in his hometo...\n\nQ: After Willard's wife died, he came back to his hometown   _   there.", "options": ["in order to date with Llah", "and got informed of Llah's husband's death", "to ask Llah to move in with him", "and was told that he needed a new pacemaker"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3085, "question": "Wild animals seem to have escaped the Indian Ocean tsunami , adding weight to ideas they possess a \"sixth sense\" for disasters, experts said on Thursday. Sri Lanka wildlife officials have said the giant waves that killed over 24,000 people along the Indian Ocean island's coast seemingly missed wild beasts, with no dead animals found. \"No elephants are dead, not even a dead hare or rabbit. I think animals can sense disaster. They have a sixth sense. They know when things are happening,\" H.D. Ratnayake, deputy director of Sri Lanka's Wildlife Department, said on Wednesday. The waves washed floodwaters up to 3 km (2 miles) inland at Yala National Park in the southeast, Sri Lanka's biggest wildlife reserve and home to hundreds of wild elephants. \"There has been a lot of evidence about dogs bar...\n\nQ: Which section does the text most probably appear in a newspaper?", "options": ["News Report.", "Discovery.", "Science Fiction.", "Culture."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2657, "question": "As the new semester begins, millions of college students across the country are trying hard to remember how best to write a paper or, more likely, how best to delay that paper. Procrastination is the thief of time and a lot of students suffer from it. They can spend whole days in the library doing nothing but staring into space, eating snacks, surfing the Internet, watching videos and looking at other students sitting around them, who, most likely, are doing nothing either. Paralyzed by their habit to procrastinate, they write micro blogs about their fears, asking their online friends if they sometimes have the same issue. But this does nothing to break the spell . According to a recent report, 95 percent of us procrastinate at some point and 20 percent of the world's population are always...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is not true?", "options": ["Procrastination makes people waste their time.", "Procrastinators usually complete their tasks perfectly.", "Speedy action is considered as a moral standard in the society.", "Procrastination is common among people."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3406, "question": "My mother, Marisol Torres, came with her family to Australia in the early 1960s. Then my parents' marriage ended and Mum began the study of precious stones. Her interest in opals took her to the New South Wales remote town of Lightning Ridge. There were no luxuries , but she was closer to nature and had a chance to find black opals and make some money. My mother was beautiful with dark hair and brown eyes, but she was also quiet and shy. Early in the Ridge years, she kept to herself, but later, she started going to the neighbourhood centre to make friends. It was her dream to mine, but her get-rich-quick thinking was unrealistic. She was cheated and she was never very successful. But she kept a sense of humour and a charming smile. Then, just as friendships began to blossom, she was diagno...\n\nQ: Lightning Ridge is a place where dreams can be fulfilled because   _  .", "options": ["there are precious stones and life is peaceful", "there are people from all walks of life", "there are rich people who can help poor people", "there is a lot of gold hidden in the ground"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2987, "question": "Hidden in a small street in the south end of Springfield, not far from buildings torn apart by the tornado earlier this year, Frigo's is an Italian restaurant right in our own backyard. Frigo's is not a tiny place. It provides different kinds of Italian food. There are refrigerator cases full of prepared foods and desserts, and shelves filled with olives and various pasta. There's some traditional Italian music and the smell is of olive oil and garlic . Above the largest refrigerator case, there's a chalk board covered with desriptions of more Italian sandwiches than I could remember. I stepped into Frigo's almost by accident when I had to stay in Springfield into the evening for an open house at the school where I work. Frigo's is the perfect place to find something quick to go. There are...\n\nQ: Who would be most likely to go to eat at Frigo's?", "options": ["People who want to eat quietly in a nice restaurant.", "People who want to enjoy home-made food", "People who like traditional American food", "People who are fond of Italian food"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1039, "question": "Do dogs understand us? Be careful what you say around your dog. It might understand more than you think. A _ named Rico recognizes the names of about 200 objects, say researchers in Germany. The dog also appears to be able to learn new words as easily as a 3-year-old child. Its word-learning skills are as good as those of a parrot or _ . In one experiment, the researchers took all 200 items that Rico is supposed to know and divided them into 20 groups of 10 objects. Then the owner told the dog to go and fetch one of the items and bring it back. In four tests, Rico got 37 out of 40 commands right. As the dog couldn't see anyone to get clues, the scientists believe Rico must understand the meanings of certain words. In another experiment, the scientists took one toy that Rico had never seen ...\n\nQ: Both experiments show that_.", "options": ["Rico is smart enough to get all commands right", "Rico can recognize different things including toys", "Rico has developed the ability of learning mathematics", "Rico won't forget the names of objects once recognizing them"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2699, "question": "BERLIN---A German woman, fearful that a burglar was trying to break into her second -storey apartment, called police after she heard someone climbing up to her balcony shortly after midnight, police said Thursday. Police discovered the \"burglar\" was a man carrying flowers and a bottle of wine who turned out to be the woman's boyfriend. But then arrested him on an outstanding reason. \"He was trying to surprise her with the flowers and a bottle of wine but it all went wrong,\" said Korbach police spokesman Volker Koenig. He said the man jumped down from the balcony and tried to escape but was quickly caught by police. \"He gave the police who were taking him to jail the bottle of wine as a gesture of thanks for the friendly treatment after the arrest. \" Koenig said. LONDON---A smoker who died ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["The sign will be printed on the packet of cigarettes.", "The signs were also shown in the windows of the hearse.", "The smoker wanted to tell people how bad it was to smoke.", "The smoker regretted forming the habit of smoking."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 265, "question": "Over the years, Brian Wansink, director of the Food and Brand Lab at Cornell University, has studied such things as how far Americans typically drive to buy food, how many times we refill our plates at all-you-can-eat buffets and how we organize our kitchens. In the mid-2000s he famously coined the phrase \"mindless eating\"(and wrote a book by that name) to focus attention on all the bad dietary decisions we make without really thinking about them. His new book, Slim by Design: Mindless Eating Solutions for Everyday Life, aims to change the design of restaurants, school lunchrooms, office cafeterias and homes so that the mindless choices we make will be more healthful ones. Some examples: Keep kitchen counters clear. No visible snack food, no bread, no nuts--not even breakfast cereal. In Wa...\n\nQ: Why did Brian Wansink write Slim by Design: Mindless eating Solutions for Everyday Life?", "options": ["Because he wanted people to become thin.", "Because he wished to change the design of public places.", "Because he hoped to coin a new phase \"mindless eating\".", "Because he intended to help people make more healthful dietary decision."], "answer": 3}]